A Guide to the William and Flora Hewlett Foundation records FA1501
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant Products, 1999-2012; 8; 10.51 Cubic Feet 8 record storage boxes
  - Global Development, 2002-2012; 4
    - GD-61 Explaining China's Development and Reforms - Hofman, Wu (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 351)
    - GD-62 Growth Challenges for Latin America: What Has Happened, Why, and How to Reform the Reforms - Ffrench-Davis (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 352)
    - GD-63 Chile's Growth and Development: Leadership, Policy-Making Process, Policies, and Results - Schmidt-Hebbel (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 353)
    - GD-64 Africa's Growth Turnaround: From Fewer Mistakes to Sustained Growth - Page (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 354)
    - GD-65 Remarks for Yale Workshop on Global Trends and Challenges: Understanding Global Imbalances - Cooper (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 355)
    - GD-66 Growth and Education - Aghion (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 356)
    - GD-67 From Growth Theory to Policy Design - Aghion, Durlauf (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 357)
    - GD-68 Eight Reason We Are Given Not to Worry About the U.S. Deficits - Frankel (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 358)
    - GD-69 A New Bretton Woods? - Rajan (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 359)
    - GD-70 Climate Change and Economic Growth - Mendelsohn (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 360)
    - GD-71 What Do We Know about Monetary Policy that Friedman Did Not Know? - Wyplosz (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 361)
    - GD-72 Climate Change, Mitigation, and Developing Country Growth - Spence (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 362)
    - GD-73 Urbanization and Growth - Spence, Annez, Buckley (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 363)
    - GD-98 The Big Book: The World's Biggest Lesson - Global Campaign for Education (2008-2100) (Box 34, Folder 364)
    - GD-M-1 Lost in Transition: Bold Ambitions, Limited Results for Human Rights under Fox - Human Rights Watch (2006-7586) (Box 34, Folder 365)
    - GD-M-2 Testimonios del derecho a saber - Audiffred (2005-6769), 2006 (Box 34, Folder 366)
    - GD-M-3 Cultura de la transparencia: primera encuesta de acceso a la informacin publica en Mxico - Pacheco Luna (2005-6769), 2006 (Box 34, Folder 367)
    - GD-M-4 Derecho de acceso a la informacin en del poder judicial - Caballero Juarez, Diaz, Villanueva (2005-6769), 2006 (Box 34, Folder 368)
    - GD-M-5 Derecho de acceso a la informacin publica parlamentaria - Nava Gomar, Luna Pla, Villanueva (2005-6769), 2006 (Box 34, Folder 369)
    - GD-M-6 Importancia social del derecho a saber - Diaz Rodriquez (2005-6769) (Box 34, Folder 370)
    - GD-M-7 IFAI y la calidad jurdica de sus decisiones - Gomez Gallardo (2005-6769) (Box 34, Folder 371)
    - GD-M-8 Manual Ciudadano de uso de la Ley de Transparencia y Acceso a la Informacin Publica Gubernamental (2005-6769), 2006 (Box 35, Folder 372)
    - GD-M-9 Indicadores de transparencia y reforma desarticulo 6 constitucional - Gomez Gallardo, Villanueva (2005-6769), 2007 (Box 35, Folder 373)
    - GD-M-10 Mexico's Right-to-Know Reforms: Civil Society Perspectives - Fox, Haight, Hofbauer (2006-7512), 2007 (Box 35, Folder 374)
    - GD-M-11 Federal Institute for Access to Information in Mexico and a culture of transparency - Sobel, Davis Knoll, Fernandez Bogato (2004-5147), 2006 (Box 35, Folder 375-376)
    - GD-M-12 Diez anos del TLCAN en Mexico - Gambrill (2002-6887), 2006 (Box 35, Folder 377)
    - GD-M-13 Insercion laboral de migrantes mexicanos y latinos en Estados Unidos - Levine (2001-6887), 2006 (Box 35, Folder 378)
    - GD-M-14 Debates sobre la guerra contra el terrorismo: una perspectiva trasatlantica - Antal (2001-6887), 2006 (Box 35, Folder 379)
    - GD-M-15 Mexico y Estados Unidos en el 2000: dos elecciones paradigmaticas - Marquez-Padilla (2001-6887), 2006 (Box 35, Folder 380)
    - GD-M-16 El movimiento chicano en el paradigma del multiculturalismo de los Estados Unidos: de pochos a chicanos, hacia la identidad - Garcia y Garcia (2001-6887), 2007 (Box 35, Folder 381)
    - GD-M-17 Alternativas energeticas para el siglo XXI - Vargas, Valdes-Ugalde (2001-6887), 2006 (Box 35, Folder 382)
    - GD-M-18 Procesos de integracion en las Americas - Gambrill (2001-6887), 2006 (Box 35, Folder 383)
    - GD-M-19 By other means for other ends? Bush's re-election reassessed - Hussain, Valdes-Ugalde (2001-6887), 2005 (Box 35, Folder 384)
    - GD-M-20 Recursos naturales estrategicos: los hidrocarburos y el agua - Vargas, Valdes-Ugalde (2002-6887), 2006 (Box 35, Folder 385)
    - GD-M-21 Dos modelos de integracion energetica: America del Norte/America del Sur - Vargas, Valdes-Ugalde (2002-6887), 2007 (Box 35, Folder 386)
    - GD-M-22 Nuevos actores en America del Norte (volumes 1 and 2) - Antal (2002-6887), 2005 (Box 35, Folder 387-388)
    - GD-M-23 Cine y propaganda para Latinoamerica: Mexico y Estados Unidos en la encrucijada de los anos cuarenta - Peredo Castro (2002-6887), 2004 (Box 35, Folder 389)
    - GD-M-24 Cambio climatico: desacuerdo entre Estados Unidos y Europa - Antal (2002-6887), 2004 (Box 35, Folder 390)
    - GD-M-25 Fronteras en America del Norte: estudios multidisciplinarios - Romero, Gutierrez Romero (2002-6887), 2004 (Box 35, Folder 391)
    - GD-M-26 One Wound for Another - Una herida por otra: testimonios de Latin@s in the U.S. through cyberspace - Joysmith, Lomas (2002-6887), 2005 (Box 35, Folder 392)
    - GD-M-27 La politica energetica estadunidense: asunto de seguridad o de mercado? - Vargas (2002-6887), 2005 (Box 35, Folder 393)
    - GD-M-28 Estados Unidos, intervencion y poder mesianico: la Guerra Fria en Guatemala, 1954 - Valdes-Ugalde (2002-6887), 2007 (Box 36, Folder 394)
    - GD-M-29 Mexico's National Human Rights Commission: a critical assessment - Human Rights Watch (2006-9090), 2008 (Box 36, Folder 395)
    - GD-M-31 Mexico abierto 2007: publicaciones y actividades (2005-6768) (Box 36, Folder 396)
    - GD-M-32 Seguridad nacional en Mxico y las relacin con estados unidos - Curzio (2002-6887), 2007 (Box 36, Folder 397)
    - GD-M-34 Clasemediero: pobre no mas, desarrollado aun no - de la Calle (2008-3138), 2010 (Box 36, Folder 398)
    - GD-M-34C Derecho y economa - Garcia y Garcia, Zavala Rubach (2007-9792), 2009 (Box 36, Folder 399)
    - GD-M-35C Situacion de los derechos humanos de las persona migrantes y solicitantes des asilo detenidas en las Estaciones Migratorias de Mexico, 2007-2009 - Sin Fronteras (2007-9784) (Box 36, Folder 400)
    - GD-M-36 Gobernar por resultados? Implicaciones de la poltica de evaluacin del desempeo del gobierno Mexicano - Gonzales (2007-1179), 2008 (Box 36, Folder 401)
    - GD-M-38 Por un Congreso con rostro: que representan los que quieren representarnos?, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 402)
    - GD-M-39 Definicion de una agenda fiscal el desarrollo de las organizaciones de la sociedad civil en Mexico (2005-6240), 2007 (Box 36, Folder 403)
    - GD-M-40 Reporte Chihuahua: anlisis del cambio de modelo en el proceso penal - Medina Perea, Araiza Reyes, Lugo Reyes (2012-5588), 2009 (Box 36, Folder 404)
    - GD-M-41 Drug War in Mexico: Confronting a Shared Threat - Shirk (2010-5588), 2011 (Box 36, Folder 405)
    - GD-M-42 Evaluating Accountability and Transparency in Mexico: National, Local, and Comparative Perspectives - Rios Cazares, Shirk (2010-5588), 2007 (Box 36, Folder 406)
    - GD-M-43 Police and Public Security in Mexico - Donnelly, Shirk (2010-5588) (Box 36, Folder 407)
    - GD-M-44 Justiciabarometro: diagnostico integral de la policia municipal de Ciudad Juarez - Moloeznik, Shirk, Suarez de Garay (2010-5588), 2011 (Box 36, Folder 408)
    - GD-M-45 Justiciabarometro: a comprehensive assessment of the municipal police of Ciudad Juarez - Moloeznik, Shirk, Suarez de Garay (2010-5588), 2011 (Box 36, Folder 409)
    - GD-M-46 Organized Crime: Beyond Drug Trafficking - ReVista (2010-5588), 2012 (Box 36, Folder 410)
    - GD-M-47 Drug Violence in Mexico: Data and Analysis through 2011 - Molzahn, Rios, Shirk (2010-5588), 2012 (Box 36, Folder 411)
    - GD-M-48 Assessing Mexico's Judicial Reform: Views of Judges, Prosecutors, and Public Defenders - Ingram, Rodriguez Ferreira, Shirk (2010-5588), 2011 (Box 36, Folder 412)
    - GD-M-49 Armed with Impunity: Curbing Military Human Rights Abuses in Mexico - Daly, Heinle, Shirk (2012-5588) (Box 36, Folder 413)
    - GD-M-50 Justiciabarometro: Survey of Judges, Prosecutors, and Public Defenders in Nine Mexican States - Ingram, Rodriguez Ferreira, Shirk (2012-5588), 2011 (Box 36, Folder 414)
    - GD-M-51 Shared Responsibility: U.S.-Mexico Policy Options for Confronting Organized Crime - Olson, Shirk, Selee (2012-5588), 2011 (Box 36, Folder 415)
    - GD-M-57 Definicion de una agenda fiscal el desarrollo de las organizaciones de la sociedad civil en Mexico (2005-6240), 2007 (Box 36, Folder 416)
  - US-Latin American Relations, 1999-2005; 5
    - LA-1 New Patterns for Mexico: Observations on Remittances, Philanthropic Giving, and Equitable Development - Merz (2004-4570), 2005 (Box 36, Folder 417-418)
    - LA-2 America's Newcomers and the Dynamics of Diversity - Bean, Stevens (1998-3258), 2003 (Box 36, Folder 419)
    - LA-3 Closing the Education Gap: Benefits and Costs - Vernez, Krop, Rydell (1995-7938), 1999 (Box 36, Folder 420)
  - Performing Arts, 2007; 6
    - PA-1 An Unfinished Canvas: Arts Education in California: Taking Stock of Policies and Practices - Woodworth, Gallagher, Campbell (2006-8573), 2007 (Box 37, Folder 421)
    - PA-2 An Unfinished Canvas: Arts Education in the San Francisco Bay Area: A Supplementary Status Report - Woodworth, Park (2006-8573), 2007 (Box 37, Folder 422)
  - Philanthropy, 2002-2010; 7
    - PH-1 Nonprofit Governance and the Sarbanes-Oxley Act - Ostrower, Bobowick (2001-6394), 2006 (Box 37, Folder 423)
    - PH-2 Nonprofit Governance in the United States: Findings on Performance and Accountability from the First National Representative Study - Ostrower (2001-6394), 2007 (Box 37, Folder 424)
    - PH-3 Providing Long-Term Services after Major Disasters - DeVita, Morley (2001-6394), 2007 (Box 37, Folder 425)
    - PH-4 After Katrina: Shared Challenges for Rebuilding Communities - DeVita (2001-6394), 2007 (Box 37, Folder 426)
    - PH-11 Borderless Giving - Global Philanthropy Forum, 2nd Annual Conference (2002-7977), 2003 (Box 37, Folder 427)
    - PH-12 Borderless Giving: Building Partnerships across Sectors - Global Philanthropy Forum, 3rd Annual Conference (2002-7977), 2004 (Box 37, Folder 428)
    - PH-13 An Information Oasis redf - Twersky (2002-8282) (Box 37, Folder 429)
    - PH-14 Panel on the Nonprofit Sector: Strengthening Transparency Governance Accountability of Charitable Organizations, A Final Report to Congress and the Nonprofit Sector (2004-5262), 2005 June (Box 37, Folder 430)
    - PH-15 Panel on the Nonprofit Sector: Strengthening Transparency Governance Accountability of Charitable Organizations, A Supplement to the Final Report to Congress and the Nonprofit Sector (2004-5262), 2006 April (Box 37, Folder 431)
    - PH-16 The Outcome Toolbox: A Practical Guide to the Nonprofit Application of Outcomes - Penna, Berger (2007-9308), 2010 (Box 37, Folder 432)
  - Population, 2006; 8
    - P-1 Public Choices, Private Decisions: Sexual and Reproductive Health and the Millennium Development Goals - Berstein, Hansen (2003-9409), 2006 (Box 37, Folder 433)
    - P-2 U.S. Foreign Assistance for Family Planning and Reproductive Health: Influences and Entry Points - Manson (2006-7832), 2006 December 5 (Box 37, Folder 434)
    - Report of the Pilot Population Program in West Africa, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 434a)
  - Special Projects, 2005-2010; 9
    - SP-1 California Road Map for a Tax and Fiscal Majority: A Values-Based Approach - Brownstein, Ito (2005-6248), 2007 May (Box 37, Folder 435)
    - SP-2 Historical Analysis of Tax and Fiscal Propositions in California: 1978-2004 - Hsu, Brownstein, Ellis-Lamkins (2005-6248), 2006 May (Box 37, Folder 436)
    - SP-3 California 2025: Taking on the Future - Hanak, Baldassare (2005-5809) (Box 37, Folder 437)
    - SP-4 California 2025: It's Your Choice - Baldassare, Hanak (2005-5809) (Box 37, Folder 438)
    - SP-5 California 2025 Publicity Folder - Baldassare, Hanak (2005-5809) (Box 37, Folder 439)
    - SP-6 Education and a Civil Society: Teaching Evidence-Based Decision Making - Callan, Grotzer (2006-7668), 2009 (Box 37, Folder 440)
    - SP-7 On the Global Nuclear Future, vols. 1-2 - Daedalus (2008-2824), 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 441)
    - SP-8 Science and Technology for America's Progress: Ensuring the Best Presidential Appointments in the New Administration - Committee on Science and Technology in the National Interest (2008-2408) (Box 37, Folder 442)
    - SP-9 Educational Progress Across Immigrant Generations in California - Reed, Hill, Jepsen (2003-8854), 2005 (Box 37, Folder 443)
    - SP-10 Changing Course: A New Direction for U.S. Relations with the Muslim World - Leadership Group on U.S.-Muslim Engagement (2006-8867), 2008 September (Box 37, Folder 444)
    - SP-15 Small Changes Big Results for the World's Poor - Boston Review (2009-4334), 2011 (Box 37, Folder 445)
    - SP-17 Presidency: Preserving Our Institutions: The Second Report of the Continuity of Government Commission: Presidential Succession (2003-9530), 2009 (Box 37, Folder 446)
- San Diego School Reform, 1998-2004; 9; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  - Implementing Standards-Based Reform in San Diego Schools: Update Report - Barbara Neufeld (Education Matters, Inc.), 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 447)
  - Compliance Investigation and Report #SS-221-00/01 (San Diego Unified School District), 2001 (Box 38, Folder 448)
  - San Diego's Big Boom: District Bureaucracy Supports Culture of Learning - Amy Hightower (Center for the Study of Teaching and Policy, University of Washington), 2001-2002 (Box 38, Folder 449)
  - San Diego City School Board of Education Memorandum - Andrew C. Porter, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 450)
  - Semi-Annual Report to the Edna McConnell Clark Foundation: Grant #00027 (San Diego City Schools Institute for Learning), 2002 (Box 38, Folder 451)
  - Building Instructional Quality: Inside-Out, Bottom Up, and Top-Down Perspectives on San Diego's School Reform - Linda Darling Hamilton, et. al, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 452)
  - A Review of San Diego's School Reform: Progress to Date and Prospects for the Future - Anthony S. Bryk and Sharon Greenberg, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 453)
  - Foundation for the Improvement of Mathematics and Science Education, Consolidated Report, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 454)
  - San Diego Administrator and Principal Surveys (Stanford University, Center for the Study of Teaching and Policy), 2000 (Box 38, Folder 455)
  - California Standards Test Results, 1998-2002 (Box 38, Folder 456)
  - Stanford Achievement Test Results, 1998-2000 (Box 38, Folder 457)
  - Comprehensive Study of District's Remedial Reading Programs and their Affect on Under-Performing Students, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 458)
  - SDUSD Demographic Information, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 459)
  - San Diego City Schools' Reform Initiative: Views from Inside Schools - Amy M. Hightower, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 460)
  - Instructional Leadership and Systemic High School Reform: The Role of the School District - Jennifer L. Husbands, 2001-2003 (Box 38, Folder 461)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 462)
  - Encanto Elementary School Profile, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 463)
  - Hewlett Foundation, San Diego Evaluation Meeting, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 464)
  - Hewlett Foundation, San Diego Evaluation Meeting Photographs, 2002 (Box 38)
  - Center for the Study of Teaching and Policy Study and Recommendations, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 465)
  - San Diego City Schools Information - Angier Elementary Schools: Work Plan, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 466)
  - San Diego Latino Coalition of Education, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 467)
  - School Variation and Systemic Instructional Improvement in Community School District #2, New York City - Richard Elmore and Deanna Burney, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 468)
  - Continuous Improvement in Community District #2, New York City - Richard Elmore and Deanna Burney, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 469)
  - Building a Learning Community: The Story of New York City Community School District #2 - Kate Maloy, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 470)
  - Professional Development and the Achievement Gap in Community School District #2 - Michael Harwell, et al., 2000 (Box 39, Folder 471)
  - The Evaluation of the National School District and Networks Grant Program, undated (Box 39, Folder 472)
  - San Diego Research and Evaluation Comments, 2000-2001 (Box 39, Folder 473)
  - Developing a Research Agenda Related to San Diego School Reforms: Proposed Workplan - Andy Porter and Tom Glennan, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 474)
  - Meeting on Research and Evaluation in San Diego Schools: Briefing Materials, 2001 August 15-16 (Box 39, Folder 475)
  - San Deigo City Schools Research Conference, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 476)
  - Status Report on Implementation of the Blueprint and Related Reform Activities, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 477)
  - Business Plan for San Diego Unified School District, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 478)
  - Developing Principals as Instructional Leaders - Elaine Fink and Lauren Resnick, undated (Box 39, Folder 479)
  - Funder Meeting on San Diego Schools and Implementation of the Blueprint, 2002 February 27 (Box 39, Folder 480)
  - Blueprint for Student Success - Executive Summary, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 481)
  - Business Plan Reviews, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 482)
  - Blueprint for Success - Matrix of Strategies, 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 483)
  - Blueprint for Success - Process Staff, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 484)
  - Blueprint for Student Success - The American Institute of Research, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 485-486)
  - San Diego Achievement Forum: Achievement in San Diego City Schools: A Progress Report, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 487)
  - Education Reform in San Diego City Schools: Progress Report, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 488)
  - Articles, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 489)
  - Community Engagement Around San Diego Unified's Reform Program, undated (Box 40, Folder 490)
  - Not Without Talented Teachers: The Distribution of Teaching Capacity in San Diego County - Scott Grimes, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 491)
  - Educational Leadership Development Academy, undated (Box 40, Folder 492)
  - From Blueprint to Reality: San Diego's Education Reforms - Betts, Zau, King (Public Policy Institute of California), 2005 (Box 40, Folder 493)
- Bay Area School Reform Collaborative (BASRC), 1994-2004; 10; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes
  Hewlett Foundation involvement with the Annenberg Challenge and BASRC grants that originated from the Annenberg and Hewlett contracts.
  - Binder, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 494-496)
    Working Group membership; Annenberg strategy and parameters; Funding proposal; Project manager; Meeting notes; Format example; DPG (David P. Gardner); Eric Schaps; Ted Mitchell; Los Angeles Proposal; New York City Proposal; Chicago Proposal; Coalition for Essential Schools; News Articles; Nation at Risk; Joint Venture Silicon Valley; Journal Articles; ECS Reality Check and other materials (Education Commission of the States); Goals 2000 (Riley speech at ECS); Reforms comparison.
  - Original Contract, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 497)
  - Contract - Administrative, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 498)
  - Contract and Related Materials, 1995-2000 (Box 41, Folder 499)
    Final contract; Interpretations; Amendments; Review of Final Drafts; Board of Trustees Review; Annenberg response; RFB Interpretation memo; Conference Call results; Conference call 7/27/95; RFB to Henrich 7/26/95; Annenberg xraft 7/21/95; HF to Annenberg 7/16/95; Opening Draft 5/10/95; Renewal for 2001-2006.
  - Verification and Matchable Grants, 1995-1997 (Box 42, Folder 500-503)
    Grant alignment forms for schools to earn a matching grant.
  - After the Test: How Schools are Using Data to Close the Achievement Gap - Kiley Walsh, Springboard Schools, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 504)
  - Mid-Year Report, 1995-1996 (Box 42, Folder 505)
  - William R. Hewlett, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 506)
  - Annenberg Challenge, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 507)
  - Hewlett-Annenberg Contract, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 508)
  - Press Conference Announcing BASRC, 1995 May 17 (Box 43, Folder 509)
  - By-Laws, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 510)
  - IRS 501(c)3 Determination, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 511)
  - Financial Reports, 1997-1999 (Box 43, Folder 512)
  - Annual Reports, 1995-2000 (Box 43, Folder 513)
  - BASRC Leadership, San Francisco Unified School District, 1996-1998 (Box 43, Folder 514)
  - Third Year Report, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 515-516)
  - Evaluations, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 517-518)
  - Walter H. Annenberg's Challenge to the Nation: A Progress Report, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 519)
  - Memo - Discretionary Planning Grant, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 520)
  - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 521)
    Board list, work plan for Spring/Summer 1995; working group membership; draft Common Commitments of BASRC Support Providers; memos regarding meetings; draft mission statement and description of support providers; meeting agendas, notes.
  - Board Background Book, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 522-523)
  - Support Provider Meeting and Member List, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 524)
  - Media References, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 525)
  - Funders' Learning Community Brown Bag Lunch, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 526)
  - District Membership Scoring Rubric, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 527)
  - Membership Mailings, 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 528)
  - Walter H. Annenberg's Challenge to the Nation: A Progress Report, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 529)
  - Memo - Funding Request and Operational Questions, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 530)
  - Hewlett-Annenberg Challenge Annual Report, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 531)
  - An Initial Look at the Bay Area School Reform Collaborative: The first six months of leadership funding and program activities - Becky Crowe, Center for Research on the Context of Teaching [CRC], Stanford University, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 532)
  - School/University Partnership Initiative - Application and Scoring Rubric, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 533)
  - Technology in Education Reform Task Force, undated (Box 45, Folder 534)
  - Program Director's Grant Files, 1996-1997 (Box 45, Folder 535)
  - CRC 2 Year Report - Assessing Results: The BASRC, Year Two, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 536)
  - Hewlett-Annenberg Challenge Annual Report, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 537)
  - Schools at Work:1998 Bay Area School Reform Collaborative Assembly Program Guide (Box 45, Folder 538)
  - The Lingo: Annenberg Challenge, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 539)
  - Report from the Bay Area High School Task Force: Rethinking the High School Leadership Model and How We Prepare People to Lead High Schools into the 21st Century, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 540)
    1. Report 2. Hewlett Foundation Funding Proposal 3. Program Description 4. Themes and Essential Questions 5. Tentative Syllabi for Courses to be Taught During 1999-2000 6. Rubric for Knowledge and Skill Development. 7. Tentative Syllabi for Courses to be Taught During 1999-2000. 8. Exit Portfolio Expectations 9. Sample Agendas for Monthly Principal Breakfast Meetings 10. Sample Agendas for Quarterly Superintendent Meetings
  - Background Essays, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 541)
  - Why think Regionally; What is Our Vision for 2006; Who Are Our Partners? Who Shares the Vision? And What Partners Do We Need?, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 542)
  - Semiannual Report for Gail Levin, Annenberg Foundation, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 543)
  - Assessing Results: The Bay Area School Reform Collaborative, Year Three, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 544)
  - Measuring Up! Program, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 545-546)
  - Hewlett-Annenberg Challenge Annual Report, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 547)
  - Annual Report of the Bay Area School Reform Collaborative: Theory of Action, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 548)